A Guide to the Opal David Papers 1970-1999
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Opal David Papers 1970-1999
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10971-a
300 items
These additional papers of Opal David concern the League of Women Voters and consist chiefly of publications and memoranda of the Virginia League and the Charlottesville-Albemarle League and its Government Committee.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was given to the Library by David Lagomarsino, Hanover, N.H. on August 26, 1999.
Biographical/Historical Information
Opal David was an Albemarle County, Va., politician and public servant.
Scope and Content Information
These additional papers of Opal David concern the League of Women Voters and consist chiefly of publications and memoranda of the Virginia League and the Charlottesville-Albemarle league and its Government Committee.
Topics include Albemarle County-Charlottesville cooperation, voting rights, the city council mixed ward proposal, and reapportionment and redistricting.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by subject.
Contents List
- Action 1978 & 1982 (Box 1)
- Brochures re the Virginia General Assembly 1982-1987 (Box 1)
- Bulletins of the League of Women Voters ca. 1973-1985 (Box 1)
- Campaign Financing 1972-1978 (Box 1)
- City-County Cooperation Survey 1977-1983 (Box 1)
- Congress 1971-1973, 1981 (Box 1)
- Congress & the Budget 1979, 1991 (Box 1)
- Constitutional Amendment by Convention 1978 (Box 1)
- District of Columbia Voting Rights 1982 (Box 1)
- Education Committee 1982 (Box 1)
- Election Guides 1982-1988 (Box 1)
- Government Committee of the Charlottesville-Albemarle League of Women Voters - Notebook ca. 1977-1982 (Box 1)
- Government Committee State Program Items 1982-1983 (Box 1)
- Impact on Issues 1984-1986 1984 (Box 1)
- "Know Your Community" 1972-1976 (Box 1)
- Memoranda of the League of Women Voters of Virginia 1983 (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous Issues 1977-1987 (Box 1)
- Mixed Ward Proposal 1977-1981 (Box 1)
- News clippings & Obituaries 1988, 1999 (Box 1)
- The Presidency 1980 & n.d. (Box 1)
- Publication Information of the League of Women Voters 1980-1988 (Box 1)
- Reapportionment & Redistricting 1964, 1981-1984 (Box 2)
- Trade Reform Legislation ca. 1982-1987 (Box 2)
- The Virginia Local Legislator 1972 (Box 2)
- Virginia Property Tax 1973-1980 (Box 2)
- Voter Information 1982-1990 (Box 2)
- Voting Rights Extension 1982 (Box 2)